

Designer. Developer. Problem solver.

linkedin.com/in/nickbravodev

PERFORMANCE PROFILE

Designer and developer with proven teamwork and leadership experience. Successfully implemented projects by structuring project requirements efficiently. Produced effective print and digital assets and built converting websites, digital products, and frontends with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Strong Proficiency in Figma and Visual Studio Code, master of Adobe XD, Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop.

HARD SKILLS

- Graphic / Layout Design
- Responsive Design
- **Product Design**
- UI/UX Design
- Adobe XD
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe Photoshop
- Fiama
- HTML / CSS / JavaScript

SOFT SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Visual Content Creation
- **Decision Making**
- Team Leadership
- Strategic Planning
- Interpersonal Communication
- Critical Thinking
- Presentations

EXPERIENCE

PRINCIPAL WEB DEVELOPER

MAVERIK. JUL 2023 - PRESENT

· As the principal (and only) web developer, I'm responsible for the entirely new codebase and architecture of all Maverik and Kum & Go web properties.

WEB DEVELOPMENT CONSULTANT

ASTROPOST. MAR 2022 - PRESENT

· I consult clients and build high performing web architectures with headless CMS integration.

FREELANCE DESIGNER / DEVELOPER

FREELANCE, 2007 - 2022

I designed and built engaging websites, user interfaces, visual identities, digital products, and online assets.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER / WEB DEVELOPER

8FISH. 2008 - 2009

 Elevated brands by designing brand identities, web and print graphics, websites, social media content, and other digital media assets.

POLICE OFFICER

POLICE DEPARTMENT, 2021 - 2023

 Contributed to educational and community outreach campaigns as the liaison between the police department and the marketing department.

POLICE DETECTIVE

POLICE DEPARTMENT. 2015 - 2021

Developed and supervised a comprehensive firearm deployment and training program and impacted lives through empathetic communication and complete criminal investigations.

POLICE LIEUTENANT

POLICE DEPARTMENT. 2010 - 2015

- · Improved transparency and community relationships by building the department's first website and social media channels and providing timely press releases.
- Developed Reserve Officer program that slashed personnel budget by 30%.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE / DIGITAL CINEMATOGRAPHY

UNIVERSITY

GPA 3.99 / VALEDICTORIAN

ASSOCIATE OF APPLIED SCIENCE / GRAPHIC DESIGN

COLLEGE OF